TAKUYA KOJIMA

UX DESIGNER





Mobile +4915156038327



takuya.kojima1@gmail.com



Website https://takuyakojima1ead4.myportfolio.com/

SKILLS

UX DESIGN

Competitive Analysis I User Research I Personas I Journey Maps I Wire Framing Information Architecture I Prototyping I Usability Testing

UI DESIGN

Style Guides | Design Patterns | Responsive Design | Typography | Layout

VISUAL DESIGN

Moodboards I Benchmarking I Graphic Design I Illustration I Visual & Verbal presentations I Concept Art & Design I I Color and Material Design

TOOLS

Adobe Creative Cloud Keynote Powerpoint Invision Prott Procreate Balsamiq

PROFILE

I am on a mission to create new values for users. With my background in product design, I aim to fuse physical and virtual design into a seamless whole. I meet the challenge of creating new experience for customers through a deep understanding of the users' and the market's needs.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance

03/2018 - ongoing

- Designed wireless charging system production design for laptop and office networking device for business use. Communicating with clients, as well as uncovering design needs through competitive analysis and product benchmarking
- Smartphone App UI/UX design to demonstrate hardware for TDK Corporation at an exhibition. Focus on simple design so that visitors intuitively understand how to use the device during the show

Color Designer NISSAN MOTOR CO.,LTD.,

01/2014 - 02/2018

- Created CMF design concepts for interior and exterior design of the highest selling car on the Japanese market in 48 years (Nissan Note) through a deep understanding of markets and customers
- Established design benchmarking to define the market and competitors. Then created
 the design proposal and production phase design support with engineers and suppliers
 to realize the new CMF expression in mass production
- Communicated with overseas studios about design development and helped to build a strong relationship between design studios
- Designed prize winning (in Japan and Germany) EV production and EV show cars to emphasize the progressive image of the brand
- Built a reliable relationship with suppliers and worked together with them to create prototypes on time to realize the design concept for production

Chief Designer YUKAI Engineering Inc,

09/2011 - 11/2013

- Created design concepts based on clients' orders and led the design process in the team
- Communicated with engineers overseas for production/ realization of design concepts (developed feasible tests, competitors' products evaluation)
- Designed overall of a robot vacuum cleaner (industrial design, UI/UX design, CMF design, and sound design)
- Managed the design conception of a smartphone app for Softbank Corp

EDUCATION

CAREERFOUNDRY

04/2019 - ongoing

- UX Design Immersion Course
- UI for UX Design Course
- · Voice Design for UX Course
- · Front End Development Course

BACHELOR OF DESIGN

Musashino Art University, Faculty of Industrial Design

04/2008 - 03/2010

· Victoria University of Wellington, Facility of Industrial Design

02/2006 - 11/2007